Guide to the Cornell University reports: general.
Cornell University reports: general.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University reports: general.
ARP 1506
Cornell University.
v.;
Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Various reports covering multiple aspects of University operations.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Various reports covering multiple aspects of University operations.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University; Cornell University -- Administration
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Description based on: 1958/1965; title from caption.
CONTAINER LIST
- Bound ARP 1506 volumes, ARP 1506 (Box 1)
  - ARP 1506 Volume 1 (Box 1, Volume 1)
    - Deans Report on Student Activities and Conduct, August 1, 1958
    - Faculty Report on Student Affairs, December 17, 1958
    - University Faculty Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure "Report and Recommendations on Principles of Academic Freedom and on Dismissal Legislation and Procedures"., April 21, 1960
    - Report of the Committee on Long Range Planning to the Centennial Planning Committee, March 21, 1961
    - Library Administrative Council and Library Board "The Space Requirements of the Cornell University Libraries Projected to 1975", March 1963
    - Report of the Faculty-Student Committee on the Freshman Year, May 20, 1963
    - Keast Reports, 1965
      1) Articulation of Undergraduate Studies with the Programs of the Secondary Schools
      2) Entrance Standards
      3) Inter-College Transfer
      4) Honors Programs and Independent Study
      5) (no report issued)
      6) The Grading System
      7) Orientation and Advising
      8) The Drop-Out Problem
      9) The Educational Environment
  - ARP 1506 Volume 2 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    - Kahn-Bowers Report "Report of the Faculty Committee on the Quality of Undergraduate Instruction", October 11, 1965
    - Annual Reports from the Commission on Undergraduate Education. Education., 1966-1969
    - Larson Report, "Report of the Special Committee of the University Faculty on Education", March 1967
    - Wright Report, "A Report Prepared by the President's Fire Protection Committee"·, June 5, 1967
  - ARP 1506 Volume 3 (Box 1, Volume 3)
    - Saperston Report, "Report of the University Commission on Residential Environment", June 11, 1967
    - Jensen Report, "Report of the Committee on the Review of Judicial Procedures for Student Misconduct", August 15, 1967
    - Sindler Reportp "Report of the Commission on the Interdependence of University Regulations and Local, State, and Federal Law", September
    - Report of the Faculty Council's Committee on Relations between Cornell University and CAL, March 21, 1967
    - Report of the President's Committee on CAL, March 27, 1968
    - Report of the Curtiss Committee on CAL, January 2, 1968
    - Williams Commission Report, April 1968
    - Report of the Study Committee for the Department of Buildings and Properties, May 1, 1968
    - Marcham Report, "Report to the Executive Committee of the Cornell University Board of Trustees by the Commission on Investments and Public Policy, June 1968
    - Kennedy Report, "Report of Presidential Commission on Military Training" (Also · known as ROTC Report}, December 10, 1968
    - Plane Report, "Report of the Commission on Teaching Assistants", December 16, 1968
  - ARP 1506 Volume 4 (Box 1, Volume 4)
    - Seznec Report, "Residential Colleges Committee Report", January 1969
    - Carter Report on the Cross -Burning Incident and Willard Straight Hall, May 23, 1969
    - Morison Report, "The President's Commission on Student Involvement in Decision-Making", June 11, 1969
    - Allee Report, "Report of the President's Committee on Housing and Dining", June 1969
    - Long Report, "Report of the Ad Hoc Judiciary Committee", August 28, 1969
    - Turner Report, "An Approach to Black Studies: Concept and Plan of the Africana Studies and Research Center", September 1969
    - Robertson Report, "Report of the Trustee Committee on Campus Unrest at Cornell", September 3, 1969
  - ARP 1506 Volume 5 (Box 1, Volume 5)
    - Cornell Constituent Assembly, "Summer Research Reports 1969", 1969
  - ARP 1506 Volume 6 (Box 1, Volume 6)
    - DuBois Report, "Black People and Government in Ithaca and Tompkins County", 1969
    - Risley Report, "Report of the Personnel Study Committee", February 1971
    - Mineka Report, "Report of the Library Study Committee", April 1971
- Additional ARP 1506x Reports (Box 2)
  - The School of Education of Cornell University., January 1961; ARP 1506b (Box 2)
  - Biological Sciences reports., 1963-1964; ARP 1506c (Box 2)
    Biology At Cornell, Robert Morison
    Recommendations from Dale Corson to President Perkins
  - Arts and Sciences report, 1965; ARP 1506d (Box 2)
  - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center documents, 1978; ARP 1506e (Box 2)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Long-range planning report., January 1960; ARP 1506f (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous papers volume (Only papers 1-18 appear to be present), 1959-1965; ARP 1506g (Box 2)
    - 1. "A Faculty Appointment Policy for Cornell." University Faculty Committee on Long Range Planning, December 1, 1959
    - 2. "A Report on Plans for the Future - Willard Straight Hall." Edgar A. Whiting., April 9, 1960
    - 3. "Adult Education at Cornell University." Parrish Committee., 1969
    - 4. "The Responsibilities and Functions of Cornell Unites Religious Works", March 1, 1961
    - 5. "Background Paper on Patterns of Instruction." Centennial Planning Committee., March 1, 1961
    - 6. "The Place of Atheistic in the University. Robert Kane., March 1, 1961
    - 7. "The Role of the Student Untion in the University Community." Edgar Whiting., March 1, 1961
    - 8. "Policy on Inviting Persons Under Indictment to Speak on the Cornell Campus." Thomas Mackessey., December 13, 1961
    - 9. "Faculty Status of Visiting Professors and Acting Professors." Thomas Mackesey., September 20, 1962
    - 10. "The Status of Research Personnel Employed by Cornell University." Committee on Membership of the University Faculty., October 20, 1962
    - 11. "Off Campus Housing" University Proctor, probably Lowell George., January 8, 1965
    - 12. "General Guidelines for Cornell's Future." President Perkins., March 29, 1965
    - 13. "Recommendations of the Provost's Ad Hoc Committee on the Campus Store.", April 15, 1965
    - 14. "Proposals of the Committee on Education." Students for Education., March 24, 1965
    - 15. "Suggestions for a Student Housing Program for Cornell." Thomas Mackesey., April 29, 1965
    - 16. "Recommendations from the Cornell University Faculty-Student Administration Forum, May 11, 1965
    - 17. "The Role of the student Union in the University Community." Edgar Whiting., March 1, 1961
    - 18. "Non-Curricular Programs of the University." John Summerskill., March 1961
    - 19. "Report on Student Housing." Faculty Committee on Student Affairs., ca. 1961
    - 20. "International Interests of Cornell University." Lauriston Sharp., March 22, 1961
    - 21. "Educational Opportunities in the Freshman Year." Bart Conta., ca. 1961
    - 22. "Admission of the Undergraduate to the University." Donald Moyer., March 1961
    - 23. "Academic Advising in the University." David Novarr., ca. 1961
    - 24. "Honors Work at Cornell." Arthur M. Mizener., ca. 1961
    - 25. "Medical Services at Cornell for Students, Faculty and Employees." Norman S. Moore. (Missing from binder, available as ARP 412)), ca. 1961
    - 26. "Assessment of Graduate Education" Dale Corson., May 27, 1966
    - 27. Report of the Study Committee for the Department of Buildings & Properties, May 1, 1968
  - Graduate School reports, 1965-1966; ARP 1506h (Box 2)
    Report to the President from the Dean of the Graduate School
    1966 Reports
    A Long Look at the Cornell University Graduate School, a Personal Statement by the Dean of the Graduate School
  - A report to the trustees of Cornell University by Dale R. Corson., March 1978; ARP 1506i (Box 2)
  - Home Economics reports, 1966-1968; ARP 1506j (Box 2)
    Final Report of the President’s Committee to Study the College of Home Economics
    Report to President James A. Perkins from the Organization Committee
  - Engineering reports, 1950; ARP 1506k (Box 2)
    Report on the College of Engineering AT Cornell University by S. C. Hollister.
    The Next Ten to Twnty Years in Engineering Education at Cornell University by Dale R. Corson
  - Report of the Director of the Priorities Study to President Dale R. Corson, June 27, 1975; ARP 1506l (Box 2)
  - Reports on the arts at Cornell, 1967-1968; ARP 1506m (Box 2)
    The Place of the Arts and Their Practice in Cornell University
    A Report to the President of Cornell University from the Universiy Committee on the Arts
    Ad-Hoc Committee on the Arts, a Report to the Faculty Council
    Recommendations on the Arts to President Perkins
  - The New York State College of Agriculture and the next quarter century., 1967; ARP 1506n (Box 2)